♪ It's tearing up my
heart when I'm with you ♪
♪ But when we are apart, I feel it, too ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ Hey ♪
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Baby, I don't understand ♪
♪ Just why we can't be lovers ♪
♪ Things are getting out of hand ♪
♪ Trying too much, but baby, we can win ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ If you want me, girl, let me know ♪
♪ I am down on my knees ♪
♪ I can't take it anymore ♪
♪ It's tearing up my
heart when I'm with you ♪
♪ But when we are apart, I feel it, too ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Baby, don't misunderstand ♪
♪ What I'm trying to tell you ♪
♪ In the corner of my mind ♪
♪ Baby, it feels like
we're running out of time ♪
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ If you want me, girl, let me know ♪
♪ I am down on my knees ♪
♪ I can't take it anymore ♪
♪ It's tearing up my
heart when I'm with you ♪
♪ But when we are apart, I feel it too ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ Tearing up my heart and soul ♪
♪ We're apart, I feel it, too ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ Tearing up my heart
and soul, all right ♪
♪ We're apart, I feel it, too ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ It's tearing up my
heart when I'm with you ♪
♪ So when we are apart, I feel it, too ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ And no matter what I
do, I feel the pain ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
(gentle pop music)